(Vet:)I'm sorry, is this a joke to you?
(Sheldon:)No.
(Leonard:)Maybe to her.
(Vet:)How big a box of chocolate was it?
(Penny:)Something like this. I don't know.
It cams free with a full tank of gas.
(Leonard:)Really? Do you know how much
those Lakers tickets were?
(Penny:)-Do you know how much gas is?
-Hey!
(Amy:)-Sorry.
-Sorry.
(Raj:)Oh, my God, Cinnamon,
are you OK?!
I can't believe you two!
(Raj:)You do whatever it takes
to save her life.
(Raj:)If she needs new organs,
I'll buy any dog necessary
and scrap them for parts!
(Vet:)-You're the owner?
-Owner, father, soul mate,
(Raj:)and if anything happens to her,
your worst nightmare!
(Vet:)Well, she's not throwing up,
which is a good sign.
(Vet:)So, I'm gonna take her in back,
put her on fluids
(Vet:)and give her something
to absorb the toxins.
OK. OK, thank you.
(Raj:)If she's scared, you can sing to her.
She likes Katy Perry.
But don't do "Firework"
That gets her all riled up.